celebrating girl amanda started a brand new subscription tier on patreon okay upward expansion
and growth it's got small doses videos every week plus extended clips of me doing what i do
moving the crowd and bonus clips from her screenings of me her political comedy documentary
she did it herself with her own money okay so we got the podcast we got the politics
understand uh what about the lifestyle you know like living i mean you're not wrong girl i talk
about self-improvement on the podcast but you'll be about it like in real life hd 4k well according
to this it looks like you're actually in the next tier up uh well seals the deal the in the man that
we trust here that's my hood yep it says right here lifestyle content her travel vlogs amanda on the
move unlimited access to her political comedy documentary in amanda we trust that's you
and full videos of her shows on the road that's me that's me y'all okay i like the sound of this
amanda is on the move i'll see y'all have this in the clouds tsa pre-check and remember if you in a
window seat that's your window that's your window
that's your window